[
  {
    "ID": 35343,
    "question": "What is the connection between John Davis (the one whose date of birth is 1787-01-13) to Governor of Massachusetts? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Unclear or no connection.",
    "new_answer": "John Davis was a Governor.",
    "ground_truth": "['position held']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 37022,
    "question": "Which is longer, Back to the Future Part III or Beauty and the Beast (the one whose Giphy username is beautyandthebeast)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nBeauty and the Beast.",
    "new_answer": "Back to the Future Part III.",
    "ground_truth": "['Beauty and the Beast']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 1859,
    "question": "What was The Nun's Story, which was nominated for the Academy Award for Best Picture, about? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nNun's crisis of faith.",
    "new_answer": "Nun's struggles with faith.",
    "ground_truth": "['32nd Academy Awards']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 59110,
    "question": "Which community college has ISNI 0000 0004 0401 5568? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Unknown.",
    "new_answer": "Answer not available, insufficient information.",
    "ground_truth": "['Pasadena City College']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 68192,
    "question": "How long is The Station Agent? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "1 hour 29 minutes.",
    "new_answer": "88 minutes.",
    "ground_truth": "['88 minute']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 24487,
    "question": "Which movie is shorter, Calendar Girls or Howard the Duck (the one that was nominated for Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Supporting Actor)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Howard the Duck.",
    "new_answer": "Calendar Girls is shorter.",
    "ground_truth": "['Calendar Girls']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 80052,
    "question": "Which TV series titled Star Wars: The Clone Wars features the voice of Liam Neeson ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "None.",
    "new_answer": "Liam Neeson voices Qui-Gon Jinn.",
    "ground_truth": "['Star Wars: The Clone Wars']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 23749,
    "question": "What is the connection between Thomas Alva Edison to diabetes mellitus? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Edison had diabetes mellitus.",
    "new_answer": "Edison had diabetes mellitus.",
    "ground_truth": "['cause of death']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 39848,
    "question": "What is the connection between Helena (the one that origins from Germany) to silent film? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Actress in silent films.",
    "new_answer": "Acted in German silent films.",
    "ground_truth": "['genre']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 66204,
    "question": "What is the postal code of London School of Economics's headquarters in London (the one that is the narrative location of Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "WC2A 2AE",
    "new_answer": "WC2A 2AE.",
    "ground_truth": "['WC2A 2AE']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 84960,
    "question": "Which ISNI is matched to the person whose CANTIC-ID is a10434926? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nUnknown.",
    "new_answer": "ISNI not available for CANTIC-ID a10434926.",
    "ground_truth": "['0000 0001 1944 6473']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 78489,
    "question": "How is Spinefarm Records related the to the heavy metal genre of music? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nSpinefarm Records specializes in metal.",
    "new_answer": "Finnish label specializing in metal.",
    "ground_truth": "['genre']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 92873,
    "question": "Which ethnic group is Dakota County's namesake? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Dakota Sioux.",
    "new_answer": "Dakota Native Americans.",
    "ground_truth": "['Sioux']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 81276,
    "question": "What's the Van Johnson's CANTIC-ID ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Unknown.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown, no available information.",
    "ground_truth": "['a10814383']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 13555,
    "question": "How is port related to DL-glutamic acid? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nNot related.",
    "new_answer": "No direct relation exists.",
    "ground_truth": "['nutrient']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 46334,
    "question": "What language is associated with the official website http://www.imagine-entertainment.com/ for the film production company that is the production studio of The Doors (that has Kathleen Quinlan as a cast member)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "English.",
    "new_answer": "English.",
    "ground_truth": "['English']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 29860,
    "question": "What is the Hornbostel-Sachs classification of the guitar whose famous people is Maurice Gibb? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nChordophone, fretted, plucked.",
    "new_answer": "Chordophone, stringed instrument.",
    "ground_truth": "['321.322-5']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 77858,
    "question": "What is the language of the official website of St. Johnstone F.C., http://www.perthstjohnstonefc.co.uk/? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "English.",
    "new_answer": "English.",
    "ground_truth": "['English']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 61008,
    "question": "Which human has an ISNI of 0000 0001 0912 7460 and is the director of The Bodyguard (whose director is Joseph Barbera)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Mick Jackson.",
    "new_answer": "Mick Jackson.",
    "ground_truth": "['Joseph Barbera']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 98734,
    "question": "Tell me the relation between Los Angeles and Alicia Silverstone (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nBorn in Los Angeles.",
    "new_answer": "Born and raised in LA.",
    "ground_truth": "['residence']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 13200,
    "question": "What landform has GeoNames feature code U.MTU? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Mountain.",
    "new_answer": "Mountain.",
    "ground_truth": "['mountain']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 89016,
    "question": "What instrument class was or is used by Bappi Lahiri ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Bollywood film music.",
    "new_answer": "Bollywood film music composer.",
    "ground_truth": "['tabla']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 69221,
    "question": "What is the relationship between Universal Pictures (the one whose official website is http://www.universalpictures.com/) and California (the one that is the narrative location of Frost/Nixon)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nUniversal Pictures is based in California.",
    "new_answer": "Film production in California.",
    "ground_truth": "['country']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 87853,
    "question": "What is the motto text for the US State that contains Franklin County with 1491 square kilometre area? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\"In God We Trust\"",
    "new_answer": "\"In God We Trust.\"",
    "ground_truth": "['Agriculture and Commerce']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 34272,
    "question": "Which visual artwork produced by Anna Faris is titled The House Bunny? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Movie.",
    "new_answer": "Film produced by Anna Faris.",
    "ground_truth": "['The House Bunny']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 8057,
    "question": "What is the relationship between Big Fish and the Broadcast Film Critics Association Award for Best Film? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Big Fish won the award.",
    "new_answer": "Big Fish won BFCA Best Film.",
    "ground_truth": "['nominated for']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 86849,
    "question": "What is the anime tv arrangement that determines the visual work of art whose title is Speed Racer (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Speed Racer.",
    "new_answer": "Speed Racer, anime TV series.",
    "ground_truth": "['Speed Racer']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 94098,
    "question": "How is (association football) soccer's Michael Bell related to Wycombe Wanderers F.C.? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Chairman of Wycombe Wanderers.",
    "new_answer": "Former chairman of Wycombe Wanderers.",
    "ground_truth": "['member of sports team']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 40830,
    "question": "What is connection between WWE SmackDown and Adult Swim? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nThere is no connection.",
    "new_answer": "No connection exists between them.",
    "ground_truth": "['original network']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 50259,
    "question": "Between Brothers that originated in Denmark or Cleopatra released in the People's Republic of China, which is longer? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Cleopatra is longer.",
    "new_answer": "Cleopatra is longer.",
    "ground_truth": "['Cleopatra']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 105906,
    "question": "What does The Flintstones in Viva Rock Vegas have to do with dinosaur? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Dino is their pet dinosaur.",
    "new_answer": "Dinosaurs are featured characters.",
    "ground_truth": "['main subject']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 21631,
    "question": "What is the connection between Odense and Katowice? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "No direct connection exists.",
    "new_answer": "No direct connection exists.",
    "ground_truth": "['twinned administrative body']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 97796,
    "question": "Which show has fewer episodes, Twin Peaks (the one that is shot in Washington) or Bad Teacher (the one that is originally aired on CBS)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Bad Teacher.",
    "new_answer": "Bad Teacher has fewer episodes.",
    "ground_truth": "['Bad Teacher']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 36370,
    "question": "What written work do we know wwhose  OCLC control number is 15143852 and whose ISBN-10 is 0-330-24382-9 ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Unknown without additional information.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown without more information.",
    "ground_truth": "['Jaws']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 4667,
    "question": "How is the guitarist Adam Horowitz related to the guitar? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "He plays it.",
    "new_answer": "Adam Horowitz plays the guitar.",
    "ground_truth": "['instrument']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 96301,
    "question": "What is the census-designated place that shares its southwest border with the United States city whose motto Justitia Omnibus? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nBoquillas del Carmen.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown, insufficient information.",
    "ground_truth": "['Silver Spring']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 97943,
    "question": "What is the official website of the television station that originally broadcasted Roots (which has Laurence Fishburne as a cast member)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "ABC.com",
    "new_answer": "Roots original broadcaster's website.",
    "ground_truth": "['http://www.history.com/']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 39312,
    "question": "What is the Hornbostel-Sachs classification of hurdy-gurdy? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nChordophone, wheel-driven, key-operated.",
    "new_answer": "Chordophone, wheel-turned.",
    "ground_truth": "['321.321-72']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 49949,
    "question": "How is Coolio related to West Coast hip hop? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Pioneering rapper and artist.",
    "new_answer": "West Coast hip hop pioneer.",
    "ground_truth": "['genre']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 104511,
    "question": "Elizabeth McGovern won a Screen Actors Guild Award for Outstanding Performance by an Ensemble in a Drama Series for which work? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Downton Abbey.",
    "new_answer": "\"Downton Abbey\"",
    "ground_truth": "['Downton Abbey']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 5908,
    "question": "Which film has the longer runtime, An Education or Julia (distributed by StudioCanal)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nJulia (StudioCanal) is longer.",
    "new_answer": "\"Julia has longer runtime.\"",
    "ground_truth": "['Julia']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 26369,
    "question": "Which movie is shorter, Napoleon Dynamite or The Jetsons Meet the Flintstones? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Napoleon Dynamite.",
    "new_answer": "Napoleon Dynamite is shorter.",
    "ground_truth": "['Napoleon Dynamite']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 63941,
    "question": "What is Draco Rosa's official website? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "dracorosa.com",
    "new_answer": "dracorosa.com",
    "ground_truth": "['http://phantomvox.com/']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 7999,
    "question": "What is the relationship between Sven Nykvist and Swedish? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Sven Nykvist was Swedish.",
    "new_answer": "Sven Nykvist was a Swedish cinematographer.",
    "ground_truth": "['languages spoken, written or signed']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 105358,
    "question": "Hotel Rwanda was nominated for an Academy Award for Best Actor for which individual? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Don Cheadle.",
    "new_answer": "Don Cheadle.",
    "ground_truth": "['77th Academy Awards']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 67199,
    "question": "What is the ISO 639-2 code of the language that is a dialect of Tagalog? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\ntl",
    "new_answer": "tl (Tagalog)",
    "ground_truth": "['fil']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 55478,
    "question": "Whose work on Greystoke: The Legend of Tarzan, Lord of the Apes earned an Academy Award nomination for Best Makeup and Hairstyling? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Rick Baker.",
    "new_answer": "Rick Baker.",
    "ground_truth": "['57th Academy Awards']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 38789,
    "question": "Which movie is shorter, Radio (the one that has S. Epatha Merkerson as a cast member) or Cleopatra (the one whose duration is 100 minute)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Radio is shorter.",
    "new_answer": "Radio is shorter.",
    "ground_truth": "['Cleopatra']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 7929,
    "question": "How is Falls Church related to Fairfax County? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Located within Fairfax County.",
    "new_answer": "Enclave within Fairfax County.",
    "ground_truth": "['shares border with']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 104071,
    "question": "Which visual artwork with the official website www.miramax.com/movie/the-lookout was produced by Spyglass Entertainment? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\"The Lookout\" movie.",
    "new_answer": "Spyglass Entertainment produced The Lookout.",
    "ground_truth": "['The Lookout']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 49265,
    "question": "What is the ISNI of Ned Kelly (whose British Museum person-institution is 149332)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nNo ISNI available.",
    "new_answer": "ISNI not assigned to Kelly.",
    "ground_truth": "['0000 0001 1635 9753']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 8946,
    "question": "Which language is associated with LL-Q56590 (atj)-Missatikamekw-Katino.wav, the pronunciation audio of the city whose official name is Ville de Gatineau? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Missatikamekw-Katino.",
    "new_answer": "Indigenous language (Atikamekw).",
    "ground_truth": "['Atikamekw']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 76792,
    "question": "How is Casino Royale published on 1953-04-13 related to Casino Royale published on 1967-07-26? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Film adaptation released.",
    "new_answer": "Same book, different adaptations.",
    "ground_truth": "['derivative work']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 78657,
    "question": "What is the ISNI of the U.S. city whose native label is San Jose? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nNo ISNI for cities.",
    "new_answer": "Answer not available.",
    "ground_truth": "['0000 0004 0638 8448']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 39789,
    "question": "Which ISNI code matches to the person with Munzinger IBA number 00000024226? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nNo answer provided. The ISNI code cannot be determined without additional information.",
    "new_answer": "ISNI: 0000 0001 2141 383X.",
    "ground_truth": "['0000 0001 0956 8901']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 66840,
    "question": "Which has the largest elevation above sea level among the comunes of Italy whose population is not 35000000? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nGran Paradiso National Park.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown without further information.",
    "ground_truth": "['Pavia']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 33459,
    "question": "What is the connection between Contraband (the one whose publication date is 1940-01-01) to English? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "English novel by Eric Ambler.",
    "new_answer": "English language wartime literature.",
    "ground_truth": "['original language of film or TV show']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 92915,
    "question": "What's the relationship between Roger Deakins and The Hurricane (based on literature)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nFilm cinematographer.",
    "new_answer": "Deakins filmed The Hurricane.",
    "ground_truth": "['director of photography']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 48466,
    "question": "What website officially represents the person with ISNI number 0000 0001 0875 4147? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nNo official website found.",
    "new_answer": "No information available.",
    "ground_truth": "['http://www.franzwaxman.com']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 34767,
    "question": "What is the ISNI of Frank Oz? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\n0000 0001 1496 8342",
    "new_answer": "ISNI: 0000 0001 1495 8349.",
    "ground_truth": "['0000 0001 1480 5270']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 77123,
    "question": "What band sets up in Bristol? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Unknown.",
    "new_answer": "Answer unclear, need more information.",
    "ground_truth": "['Portishead']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 14688,
    "question": "Which ethnic group does Adrian Grenier belong to? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "White/Caucasian.",
    "new_answer": "Adrian Grenier is of mixed ethnicity.",
    "ground_truth": "['Indigenous peoples of the United States']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 101578,
    "question": "How is Hulk (sport number 10) related to F.C. Zenit St. Petersburg? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Former player.",
    "new_answer": "Former player of Zenit St. Petersburg.",
    "ground_truth": "['member of sports team']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 73955,
    "question": "How was the population size 1,196,070 ascertained for the Ohio county corresponding to PermID 5000876244? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nCensus or estimation.",
    "new_answer": "Census or survey data used.",
    "ground_truth": "['estimation process']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 96960,
    "question": "Which film's cast includes the individual whose name in native language is Michael Rosenbaum? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2",
    "new_answer": "Michael Rosenbaum in which film?",
    "ground_truth": "['Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 29699,
    "question": "tell me the entertainment that is a derivative work of the animated film called Bolt (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nBolt video game.",
    "new_answer": "TV series and video game.",
    "ground_truth": "['Bolt']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 63100,
    "question": "Which is shorter, The Adventures of Ford Fairlane or A Civil Action? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Ford Fairlane.",
    "new_answer": "Ford Fairlane is shorter.",
    "ground_truth": "['The Adventures of Ford Fairlane']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 66290,
    "question": "What film's exploitation visa number is 129383 and official website is http://marvel.com/movies/movie/36/thor? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Thor.",
    "new_answer": "Thor.",
    "ground_truth": "['Thor']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 80200,
    "question": "What literary genre is Kick-Ass, which was published on 2010-04-22, derived from? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Superhero comic book.",
    "new_answer": "Superhero comic book series.",
    "ground_truth": "['Kick-Ass']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 102933,
    "question": "Which movie is longer, Miracle at St. Anna or Thor (the one that is shot in Los Angeles)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Miracle at St. Anna.",
    "new_answer": "Miracle at St. Anna.",
    "ground_truth": "['Miracle at St. Anna']",
    "label_type": [
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "MISC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 48513,
    "question": "Why is a border shared between Andhra Pradesh, with 28219075 urban dwellers, and Chhattisgarh, whose subreddit is Chhattisgarh? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nGeographical proximity and historical reasons.",
    "new_answer": "Geographical location and history.",
    "ground_truth": "['Andhra Pradesh Reorganisation Act, 2014']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 55052,
    "question": "Why was the Catholic sovereign state ultimately founded on 1955-10-26? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nTo protect Catholic interests.",
    "new_answer": "To protect Catholic interests.",
    "ground_truth": "['State of Vietnam referendum']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 54904,
    "question": "Why did The Fugitive (shot in North Carolina) receive an Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nTommy Lee Jones was exceptional.",
    "new_answer": "Tommy Lee Jones' outstanding performance.",
    "ground_truth": "['66th Academy Awards']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 87658,
    "question": "How come was Babe nominated for Academy Award for Best Writing, Adapted Screenplay? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nGreat screenplay adaptation.",
    "new_answer": "Great screenplay adaptation and storytelling.",
    "ground_truth": "['68th Academy Awards']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 71732,
    "question": "What is the connection between Why We Fight (the one whose color is black-and-white) to World War II? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nPropaganda film for WWII.",
    "new_answer": "Propaganda film for war effort.",
    "ground_truth": "['main subject']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 83437,
    "question": "Why is the Tokyo of Yoko Ono's birth distinct from the Tokyo where Bandai Namco Holdings was formed? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nDifferent time periods.",
    "new_answer": "Geographical and temporal differences.",
    "ground_truth": "['prefecture of Japan']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 63176,
    "question": "Why is the Tokyo where Osamu Tezuka died distinct from the Tokyo where the story of Resident Evil: Afterlife is set? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nDifferent time periods.",
    "new_answer": "Different time periods.",
    "ground_truth": "['prefecture of Japan']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 86440,
    "question": "Which has more episodes, the propaganda film Why We Fight or Looney Tunes? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Looney Tunes.",
    "new_answer": "Looney Tunes, it ran longer.",
    "ground_truth": "['Looney Tunes']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 43804,
    "question": "Which has less episodes, Infernal Affairs (whose number of episodes is 3) or Why We Fight (whose genre is propaganda film)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Infernal Affairs (3 episodes).",
    "new_answer": "Infernal Affairs has fewer episodes.",
    "ground_truth": "['Infernal Affairs']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 47415,
    "question": "Why James Cameron who uses the French language, date of birth of the person is 1954-01-01 statement should be considered deprecated? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nIncorrect or irrelevant information.",
    "new_answer": "Outdated or incorrect information.",
    "ground_truth": "['item/value with less accuracy']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 67055,
    "question": "Which movie is longer, Why We Fight (the one whose distributor is Sony Pictures Classics) or Beloved (the one whose release region is United States of America)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Beloved is longer.",
    "new_answer": "Beloved, no extended version.",
    "ground_truth": "['Beloved']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 13067,
    "question": "Regarding a city which is the birthplace of Joseph Fiennes, why should be the statement, that GSS code (2011) is E04010464,  considered depreciated ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nCode has been updated.",
    "new_answer": "Code has been updated.",
    "ground_truth": "['withdrawn identifier value']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 100257,
    "question": "Why does the statement, that the ISNI of a person buried in Ticino is  0000 0003 6864 0824, should be considered deprecated ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nISNI has been reassigned.",
    "new_answer": "ISNI code has been updated.",
    "ground_truth": "['applies to other compound']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 48140,
    "question": "Why does Australia (whose central government debt as a percent of GDP is 40.5 percentage) have diplomatic relations with East Timor? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nGeopolitical and economic interests.",
    "new_answer": "Strategic and economic interests.",
    "ground_truth": "['Australia–East Timor relations']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 79744,
    "question": "Regarding the city with the local dialing code of 0383 and official website of http://www.melbourne.vic.gov.au/ why should this statement be thought of as deprecated? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nWebsite and dialing code incorrect.",
    "new_answer": "Outdated information.",
    "ground_truth": "['item/value with less accuracy']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 25073,
    "question": "Why does Madagascar (a member of the African Union) have diplomatic relations with Indonesia? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nTrade and economic cooperation.",
    "new_answer": "Trade and economic cooperation.",
    "ground_truth": "['Indonesia–Madagascar relations']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 101706,
    "question": "For the city whose WOEID is 1100071, why was its postal code of 3350 deprecated? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nPostal code changed or updated.",
    "new_answer": "Postal code change, reason unknown.",
    "ground_truth": "['does not exactly match']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 83184,
    "question": "Tell me the movie with official website http://www.sonyclassics.com/whywefight/ and that is entitled Why We Fight (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Why We Fight.",
    "new_answer": "Movie about reasons for war.",
    "ground_truth": "['Why We Fight']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 18890,
    "question": "Why did Richard Brooks (who died from heart failure) receive an Academy Award for Best Writing, Adapted Screenplay? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nFor \"Elmer Gantry\" screenplay.",
    "new_answer": "Adapted screenplay was well-written.",
    "ground_truth": "['33rd Academy Awards']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 89631,
    "question": "Why does Macau have diplomatic relations with Hong Kong (whose inflation rate is 10 percentage)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Geopolitical and economic ties.",
    "new_answer": "Political and economic ties.",
    "ground_truth": "['Hong Kong–Macau relations']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 46574,
    "question": "Why was the National Park Service ultimately founded on 1916-08-25? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "To protect natural resources.",
    "new_answer": "To protect natural resources.",
    "ground_truth": "['National Park Service Organic Act']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 93022,
    "question": "Why did Tina Turner's US citizenship end? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nRenounced for Swiss citizenship.",
    "new_answer": "Renounced for Swiss citizenship.",
    "ground_truth": "['renunciation of citizenship']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 63715,
    "question": "Why did  James Ivory (the one that has the occupation of astronomer receive the Copley Medal? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nFor his work in astronomy.",
    "new_answer": "For his contributions to astronomy.",
    "ground_truth": "['For his various Mathematical Contributions printed in the Philosophical Transactions.']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 2074,
    "question": "Why did the Communist Party of the Soviet Union dissolve on 1991-08-29? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nCollapse of Soviet Union.",
    "new_answer": "Collapse of Soviet Union.",
    "ground_truth": "['prohibition of a political party']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 86338,
    "question": "Why was the Copley Medal given to  Carl Friedrich Gauss? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nMathematical contributions and discoveries.",
    "new_answer": "For his mathematical contributions.",
    "ground_truth": "['For his inventions and mathematical researches in magnetism.']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 67174,
    "question": "What is the number of episodes for Why We Fight (the one that mainly depicts World War II)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "7 episodes.",
    "new_answer": "Depicts reasons for World War II.",
    "ground_truth": "['7']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 71105,
    "question": "Why should we say no to a statement that the official website of American History X is http://www.historyx.com? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nIt is not accurate.",
    "new_answer": "Not the official website.",
    "ground_truth": "['offline']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 85109,
    "question": "Why was Stephen Hawking awarded the Copley Medal? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nFor his contributions to science.",
    "new_answer": "Outstanding contributions to science.",
    "ground_truth": "['For his outstanding contribution to theoretical physics and theoretical cosmology.']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 9029,
    "question": "Why was the Copley Medal given to James Ivory (the one whose name in native language is James Ivory)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nFor his mathematical contributions.",
    "new_answer": "Contributions to mathematics.",
    "ground_truth": "['For his various Mathematical Contributions printed in the Philosophical Transactions.']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 104027,
    "question": "Why did the political party abbreviated as КПГ dissolve on 1933-01-01? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nUnknown (insufficient information)",
    "new_answer": "Government crackdown on opposition parties.",
    "ground_truth": "['prohibition of a political party']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 8104,
    "question": "Why did William Blake's citizenship in the Kingdom of Great Britain come to an end? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "He died.",
    "new_answer": "He died.",
    "ground_truth": "['Acts of Union 1800']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 51802,
    "question": "Why should the ISNI 0000 0003 6864 0824 of the person having the CANTIC-ID 10453878 be considered depreciated? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nDuplicate or incorrect identifier.",
    "new_answer": "CANTIC-ID replaced ISNI.",
    "ground_truth": "['applies to other compound']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 39666,
    "question": "Why is American Pie 2 considered a teen film? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nSexual content and humor.",
    "new_answer": "High school/college-aged characters and themes.",
    "ground_truth": "['genre']",
    "label_type": [
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "WHY",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 33547,
    "question": "What is the connection between Johnny Mercer (the one whose birth name is John Herndon Mercer) to lyricist? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "He was a lyricist.",
    "new_answer": "Savannah, Georgia.",
    "ground_truth": "['occupation']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 90191,
    "question": "Where was a movie, with the official website http://www.thepassionofchrist.com/, published on 18th March 2004 ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Theaters.",
    "new_answer": "USA.",
    "ground_truth": "['Germany']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 34843,
    "question": "Which university employs Edgar Meyer (the one whose ISNI is 0000 0000 1389 936X)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Vanderbilt University.",
    "new_answer": "Vanderbilt University.",
    "ground_truth": "['University of Zurich']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 97486,
    "question": "Where was Immortals, which has a publication date of 2011-11-11, published? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Unknown.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown.",
    "ground_truth": "['Germany']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 99103,
    "question": "Of countries where the total rate of fertility is other than 5.6, which occupies the biggest area? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nRussia.",
    "new_answer": "Not enough information provided.",
    "ground_truth": "['Greenland']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 81528,
    "question": "What is the county of California having the Los Angeles in the United States of America? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Los Angeles County.",
    "new_answer": "Los Angeles County, California.",
    "ground_truth": "['Los Angeles County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 24995,
    "question": "What administrative territorial entity contains Cambridge (whose start time is 1) where Richard Attenborough was born? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "England, Cambridgeshire.",
    "new_answer": "England, UK.",
    "ground_truth": "['England']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 72702,
    "question": "Which Illinois county has the official website http://www.co.peoria.il.us? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Peoria County.",
    "new_answer": "Peoria County.",
    "ground_truth": "['Peoria County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 26725,
    "question": "What is the relation between The Scarlet Letter (the one that is part of the movement Romanticism) with Boston? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nSet in Puritan Boston.",
    "new_answer": "Set in Puritan Boston.",
    "ground_truth": "['narrative location']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 21548,
    "question": "Which visual artwork has a publication date not in 1976 and has the title Hamlet, Prinz von Dänemark? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nNone.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown.",
    "ground_truth": "['Hamlet']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 43719,
    "question": "How is the literature-based film The Sum of All Fears connected to Russia? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nNuclear bomb plot involving Russia.",
    "new_answer": "Baltimore and Chechnya.",
    "ground_truth": "['filming location']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 64111,
    "question": "Which has more people, Odessa (the one whose official website is http://www.odessa-tx.gov/) or Henderson? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Odessa has more people.",
    "new_answer": "Odessa has more people.",
    "ground_truth": "['Henderson']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 101533,
    "question": "What is the connection between Pitbull to record producer? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Pitbull is a record producer.",
    "new_answer": "Collaboration on music production.",
    "ground_truth": "['occupation']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 30834,
    "question": "Which has less elevation above sea level, Santa Ana or Bloomington whose population is 78902? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nSanta Ana.",
    "new_answer": "Bloomington has lower elevation.",
    "ground_truth": "['Santa Ana']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 42061,
    "question": "Dwayne Johnson was born in which US city? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Hayward, California.",
    "new_answer": "Hayward, California.",
    "ground_truth": "['Hayward']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 98606,
    "question": "Which has the smallest area among the Texas counties that contain Dallas whose Dewey Decimal Classification is 2--7642812? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nRockwall County.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown, requires further research.",
    "ground_truth": "['Collin County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 55629,
    "question": "Of the Texas counties with a population not of 3500000000, which is the largest in area? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nLoving County.",
    "new_answer": "Largest: Brewster County, TX.",
    "ground_truth": "['Harris County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 86851,
    "question": "What is the relationship between Victor Miller and screenwriter? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nVictor Miller is a screenwriter.",
    "new_answer": "Victor Miller is a screenwriter.",
    "ground_truth": "['occupation']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 84518,
    "question": "Which country whose total fertility rate is more than 1.2 has the largest area? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nRussia.",
    "new_answer": "Canada.",
    "ground_truth": "['Greenland']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 314,
    "question": "Among the counties of New York with population less than 760000,which one has the largest area ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nAllegany.",
    "new_answer": "Wyoming County.",
    "ground_truth": "['St. Lawrence County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 6114,
    "question": "Which as the smaller area, Leicestershire or Somerset, which contains Bath? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Leicestershire.",
    "new_answer": "Leicestershire is smaller.",
    "ground_truth": "['Leicestershire']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 66134,
    "question": "Which area is larger, Leeds (the one whose inception time is 1974-04-01) or Oldham (the one whose elevation (above sea level) is 542 metre)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nLeeds is larger.",
    "new_answer": "Leeds is larger.",
    "ground_truth": "['Leeds']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 89296,
    "question": "What is Cynthia Nixon's role in Sex and the City (which was nominated for Primetime Emmy Award for Outstanding Writing for a Comedy Series)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Miranda Hobbes.",
    "new_answer": "Miranda Hobbes, a lawyer.",
    "ground_truth": "['Miranda Hobbes']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "PER",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 54572,
    "question": "Tell me the relationship between The Count of Monte Cristo (which has a 183 minute duration) nad Marseille. (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Set in Marseille.",
    "new_answer": "Setting of the story.",
    "ground_truth": "['narrative location']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 75912,
    "question": "Which US city is the twinned administrative body of Wollongong? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Flagstaff, Arizona.",
    "new_answer": "Los Angeles.",
    "ground_truth": "['Palm Desert']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 63769,
    "question": "When did the US city where Brett Favre was born have a population of 67793? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Unknown.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown.",
    "ground_truth": "['2010-01-01']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 10748,
    "question": "Which Indiana county, whose population is not equal to 700, has the largest area? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nPulaski County.",
    "new_answer": "Largest area: Jasper County.",
    "ground_truth": "['Allen County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 4254,
    "question": "Which one has a greater elevation above sea level, Bangalore or Riyadh? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Riyadh.",
    "new_answer": "Riyadh is at higher elevation.",
    "ground_truth": "['Bangalore']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 70670,
    "question": "What is the connection between Annapolis (the one whose original language is English) to United States of America? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Capital of Maryland.",
    "new_answer": "Capital city of Maryland.",
    "ground_truth": "['country of origin']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 1061,
    "question": "Which high school with other than 80000 students has the fewest of them? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nNot specified.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown, need more information.",
    "ground_truth": "['Phillips Academy']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 98461,
    "question": "Which area is smaller, Hancock County (the one whose population is 54659) or Somerset County (the one whose population is 51824)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nHancock County is smaller.",
    "new_answer": "Hancock County is smaller.",
    "ground_truth": "['Hancock County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 14693,
    "question": "Which time zone has the short name PHT and includes the country of the Philippines? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Philippine Time (PHT).",
    "new_answer": "Philippines Time (PHT).",
    "ground_truth": "['Philippine Standard Time']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 67586,
    "question": "Which has a greater duration, Rome (whose duration is 50 minutes) or Street Fighter II V? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Street Fighter II V.",
    "new_answer": "Rome: 50 minutes.",
    "ground_truth": "['Rome']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 41700,
    "question": "Which California county is smallest by area whose population is less than 23000? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nAlpine County.",
    "new_answer": "Alpine County.",
    "ground_truth": "['Santa Cruz County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 37367,
    "question": "Which university is in New Brunswick (the one whose demonym is Néo-Brunswickois)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Université de Moncton.",
    "new_answer": "University of New Brunswick.",
    "ground_truth": "['University of New Brunswick']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 76265,
    "question": "How are The Chemical Brothers and the UK linked? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nElectronic music pioneers from UK.",
    "new_answer": "Both from the UK.",
    "ground_truth": "['country of origin']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 86109,
    "question": "What Arizona county with a population that is not 5500000000 has the smallest area? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nLa Paz County.",
    "new_answer": "Greenlee County.",
    "ground_truth": "['Santa Cruz County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 49514,
    "question": "What is the place of publication of the visual artwork titled Be Cool that was released on 2005-03-31? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Unknown.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown.",
    "ground_truth": "['Germany']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 95553,
    "question": "What is the publication territory for the visual artwork titled Babe whose release date is 1995-12-07? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Unknown.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown.",
    "ground_truth": "['Germany']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 7105,
    "question": "Which ceremonial county of England has ISO 3166-2 code of GB-NBL? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Northumberland.",
    "new_answer": "Northumberland.",
    "ground_truth": "['Northumberland']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 33415,
    "question": "The INSEE countries and foreign territories code is 99135 for which island? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Mayotte.",
    "new_answer": "Wallis and Futuna.",
    "ground_truth": "['Aruba']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 90253,
    "question": "What is the connection between Glen A. Larson to Long Beach (the one that is the birthplace of Marc Cherry)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Both born in Long Beach.",
    "new_answer": "Both from Long Beach.",
    "ground_truth": "['place of birth']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 83581,
    "question": "Which county of and in Texas, setting of Mao's Last Dancer, occupies the most area? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Brewster County.",
    "new_answer": "Brewster County.",
    "ground_truth": "['Harris County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 36226,
    "question": "Which has a greater area, Albany (the one whose population is 77434) or Laredo? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Laredo.",
    "new_answer": "Laredo has greater area.",
    "ground_truth": "['Laredo']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 50111,
    "question": "Between Barrow-in-Furness (TOID: 4000000074560818) and Southend-on-Sea, which place takes up the least area? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nSouthend-on-Sea.",
    "new_answer": "Southend-on-Sea.",
    "ground_truth": "['Southend-on-Sea']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 28944,
    "question": "Which area is larger, Illinois (the one whose demonym is Illinoisian) or Virginia (the one that is the narrative location of The Vampire Diaries)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nVirginia is larger.",
    "new_answer": "Illinois is larger.",
    "ground_truth": "['Illinois']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 37219,
    "question": "New York City, setting of The Quiet Man reviewed at 26.81%, is in which country? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "United States.",
    "new_answer": "United States.",
    "ground_truth": "['United States of America']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 96880,
    "question": "Romeo & Juliet the visual artwork whose publication date is 3-13-1997, where was it published? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Unknown.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown.",
    "ground_truth": "['Germany']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 69693,
    "question": "Which Claifornia county contains the US city whose postal code is 92270? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Riverside County.",
    "new_answer": "Riverside County.",
    "ground_truth": "['Riverside County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 13589,
    "question": "What is the capital that is the narrative location of Quo Vadis starring Deborah Kerr? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Rome.",
    "new_answer": "Rome, Italy.",
    "ground_truth": "['Rome']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 30415,
    "question": "Which administrative territorial entity is New York City, the birthplace of George Segal (the one whose IPI base code is I-001913648-0)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "City.",
    "new_answer": "New York, United States.",
    "ground_truth": "['New York']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 91796,
    "question": "What is the IETF language tag of Bulgarian? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nbg",
    "new_answer": "bg",
    "ground_truth": "['bg']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 83760,
    "question": "Which has a lower population count, Merced or Evansville? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Merced.",
    "new_answer": "Merced has lower population count.",
    "ground_truth": "['Merced']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 79233,
    "question": "What is the FIFA country code of the national association football team whose ranking is 24th on the date 2013-11-28? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nBEL.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown without additional information.",
    "ground_truth": "['GHA']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 63404,
    "question": "What city has the local-dialing code 055 and is the twinned administrative body of Tirana? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Durrës, Albania.",
    "new_answer": "Durrës, Albania.",
    "ground_truth": "['Florence']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 48132,
    "question": "What counntry didTyrone Power (the one whose official website is http://www.tyrone-power.com/biography_annabella.html) died in, if we know it happened in Madrid ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Spain.",
    "new_answer": "Spain.",
    "ground_truth": "['Spain']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 37307,
    "question": "The visual artwork titled The Texas Chainsaw Massacre was released on 2003-10-17 in which place? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "United States.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown.",
    "ground_truth": "['United States of America']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 8659,
    "question": "What is the relationship between Nick Jonas and actor? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Nick Jonas is an actor.",
    "new_answer": "No known relationship.",
    "ground_truth": "['occupation']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "PER",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 46191,
    "question": "What is the college of Rebecca Hall of the University of Cambridge (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "King's College.",
    "new_answer": "Cambridge College.",
    "ground_truth": "[\"St Catharine's College, Cambridge\"]",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "ORG",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 35859,
    "question": "Which has the most students among the schools whose student count is less than 42000? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nMIT",
    "new_answer": "Unknown without data.",
    "ground_truth": "['The Wharton School']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "ORG",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 84000,
    "question": "How is Charlotte Gainsbourg related to the profession of actor? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Family background in acting.",
    "new_answer": "She is a French actress.",
    "ground_truth": "['occupation']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 32304,
    "question": "Which cities of Pennsylvania with a population greater than 36000 has the smallest elevation (above sea level)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nChester, PA.",
    "new_answer": "Chester, PA.",
    "ground_truth": "['Philadelphia']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 86207,
    "question": "Which Dutch province contains The Hague since 1840 ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "South Holland.",
    "new_answer": "South Holland.",
    "ground_truth": "['South Holland']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 62756,
    "question": "Which United States counties have a population greater than 2500 and a FIPS 6-4 code that is 49005? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nBeaver County, Utah.",
    "new_answer": "Only Beaver County, Utah.",
    "ground_truth": "['Cache County']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 61443,
    "question": "Which has less elevation above sea level, Burnaby or Dresden whose population is 504209? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nBurnaby.",
    "new_answer": "Burnaby has lower elevation.",
    "ground_truth": "['Dresden']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 20775,
    "question": "Which city of the United States has postal code as 92051 ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Oceanside, California.",
    "new_answer": "Oceanside, California.",
    "ground_truth": "['Oceanside']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 47897,
    "question": "Which area has lower elevation above sea level, Colombo or Edmonton (the one that is the birthplace of Nathan Fillion)? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Colombo.",
    "new_answer": "Colombo has lower elevation.",
    "ground_truth": "['Colombo']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      1,
      1,
      0,
      0,
      0
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 29759,
    "question": "Where was the visual artwork that is followed by 2010: The Year We Make Contact published on 1968-05-10 ? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "Unknown.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown.",
    "ground_truth": "['London']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 29923,
    "question": "What is the connection between William Lava to Saint Paul? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "No connection.",
    "new_answer": "Both from Minnesota.",
    "ground_truth": "['place of birth']",
    "label_type": [
      2,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "LOC",
    "ground_truth_type": "LOC",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 74355,
    "question": "When did Monroe County (the one whose inception time is 1854) have a population of 45154? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "In 1920.",
    "new_answer": "Unknown, requires further research.",
    "ground_truth": "['2011-07-01']",
    "label_type": [
      3,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "DATE",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 96380,
    "question": "When was G.I. Joe: The Rise of Cobra (the one that is released for Xbox 360) published? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "2009.",
    "new_answer": "2009.",
    "ground_truth": "['2009-08-04']",
    "label_type": [
      3,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "DATE",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 98923,
    "question": "When was the 2009 Sundance Film Festival held? (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "January 15-25, 2009.",
    "new_answer": "January 15-25, 2009.",
    "ground_truth": "['2009']",
    "label_type": [
      3,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "MISC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "DATE",
    "whether_change": "False"
  },
  {
    "ID": 41052,
    "question": "Regarding the capital with the local dialing code 495 and population of 1854400 tell me the time point of it. (Limit the length of the answer to 5 words or less.) ",
    "original_answer": "\n\nMoscow, Russia - UTC+3",
    "new_answer": "Time in capital with code 495.",
    "ground_truth": "['1917-01-01']",
    "label_type": [
      3,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      0,
      1,
      1
    ],
    "original_answer_type": "LOC",
    "new_answer_type": "MISC",
    "ground_truth_type": "DATE",
    "whether_change": "True"
  },
  {
    "ID": 36679,
